A Finding Aid to the Betty Parsons Gallery records and personal papers, circa 1920-1991, bulk 1946-1983, in the Archives of American Art AAA.parsbett
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence Files, 1941-1983; Series 3; (Boxes 21-24, 52; 3.7 linear feet)
  - Individuals and Collectors, 1941-1982; 3.2
    - H, 1948-1978; (3 folders) (Box 23, Folder 35-37)
      Hoagland, Elizabeth
      Hoff, Margo
      Holbrook, Hollis
      Holmes, Reginald
      Holzer, Jane
      Hornick, Morton J.
      Hoving, Walter
      Howard, Charles
      Howard, Robert
      Howard, Sue
      Howell, Douglass
      Hughes, John Besseman
      Hunter, Sam
    - Harari, Mary McFadden, 1963-1968 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - I, 1965-1975 (Box 23, Folder 39)
      Ingersoll, Mrs. W. F.
      Interal Revenue Service
      International Bank for Reconstruction and Development
      Isaacs, Reginald
      Ittelson, Mrs. Henry
      Izbicki, Ray
    - J, 1941-1982 (Box 23, Folder 40)
      Jackson, Sarah
      Jacobson, Edward
      Jaffe, Sam
      James, Rebecca Salsbury
      Jannasch, Dr.
      Japan Air Lines, Public Relations
      Jasper, Martha
      Jaubert, Mariette Sybil
      Javits, Jacob K.
      Jenks, Thomas S.
      Johnson, Buffie
      Johnson, Jeanne
      Johnson, Lyndon B.
      Jones, Mr. and Mrs. Franklin
      Jones, Joe
      Jova, Henri V.
      Jungermann, Eva
      Junker, Howard
    - Johnson, Philip, 1954-1971 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - K, 1951-1978 (Box 23, Folder 42)
      Kahn, Mrs. Arthur
      Kardon, Robert
      Kanitz, Dr. E.
      Kasle, Gertrude
      Kaufman, Irving
      Kealy, Hinman and Susan
      Kelman, Charles
      Kennedy, Robert F.
      Keyser, Barbara
      Kilborn, Paul C.
      Kimball, Abbott
      King, Antoinette
      Kinnicutt, Frank
      Kitaj, Jeanne
      Kizhner, Michael
      Koenig, Kasper
      Kopf, Dorothy Thompson
      Koska, Zentaro
      Kostolowski, Andrej
      Kozloff, Max
      Krauss, Sophie
      Kuhl, Mary Lou
      Kumar, Ravi
      Kusama, Yayoi
    - L, 1945-1982; (2 folders) (Box 23, Folder 43-44)
      Lader, Melvin
      Lambert, Eleanor
      Langston, Basil
      Larsen, Jeanette
      Lasker, Mrs. Albert D.
      Lawrence, Mrs. Harding
      Leach, Jeffrey
      Lebron, James J.
      Lee, Albert R.
      Lee, Amy Freeman
      Leeson, Robert
      Levy, Julien
      Lewallen, Connie
      Lewis, Susan
      Liberski, B.
      Lichenstein, Ferdinand
      Liebman, Marjorie
      Liebman, Williams, Bennett, Baird and Minow
      Linker, Mr.
      Lion, Albert
      Lipman, Howard W.
      Lippard, Lucy
      Lippold, Richard
      Lloyd Mrs. H. Gates
      Long, Lois
      Lowenthal, Reeves
      Lucien, Edward
      Lukach, Joan
      Lundberg, Mary
      Lutzeier, Paul
      Lyster, Mrs. Bernard
    - Longwell, Daniel and Mary, 1957-1960 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Ludington, Wright, 1962-1967 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - M, 1949-1978 (Box 23, Folder 47-49)
      Maas, Willard
      Mackery, Frank
      Macy, Gertrude
      Maddrell, Paul W.
      Malone, Mrs. Adrian
      Mark, Grant
      Markowski, Eugene
      Matsner, Eric M.
      Matta, Malitte
      Matthews, Thomas A.
      Mayer, Jack P.
      Mazoh, Stephen
      McCarthy, Eugene
      McCloughan, Loraine
      McGinnis, Lucille
      McIntosh, Michael
      McKean, Margaret
      Melikian, Mary
      Mellon, Bunny (Mrs. Paul)
      Menkin, Marie
      Merrill, Charles
      Merrilld, Knud
      Metz, Gwen
      Meyer, J. J. De Lucio
      Meyerhoff, Natalie R.
      Miller, Dorothy
      Miller, Peter
      Miller, Mrs. C. Earl
      Miller, Richard
      Miller, Stephen R.
      Mills, Margaret
      Miner, Laura
      Mobutu, President (de la Republique de Kinshasa)
      Moline, Giselle
      Moorman, Peggy
      Morley, Grace
      Moscowitz, Morris
      Motherwell, Robert
      Mullen, Russ
      Murchison, John D.
      Murdock, Robert M.
      Murray, Natalie Danesi
      Murray, Robert
      Myers, Winslow
    - Malbin, Lydia Winston, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Mallory, Margaret, 1967-1978 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Marcus, Stanley (Neiman-Marcus), 1971-1975 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Mayer, Robert B., 1964-1971 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Meilach, Dona Z., 1965-1970 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - N, 1949-1978 (Box 23, Folder 55)
      Nakajima, Shunkichi
      Nathans, Rhoda
      National Historic Shrines Foundation, Inc.
      Nezdanov, Alexander K.
      Newhouse, S. I.
      Newman, Albert and Muriel
      Nickel, Jim
      Niester, Sibylle
      Nishii, Masaki
      Nordness, Lee
      Nordstrom, Lars-Gunnar
      Northey, John
      Northrup, Lila Tomlin
    - Newberry, John S., 1960-1965; (2 folders) (Box 23, Folder 56-57)
    - Newhouse, James K., 1964-1967 (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - O, 1962-1977 (Box 23, Folder 59)
      O'Connor, Francis
      O'Shaughnessy, Michael
      Oakes, Francis W.
      Hotel Okura
      Osborn, Robert
    - P, 1951-1978; (2 folders) (Box 23, Folder 60-61)
      Paine, Stephen
      Pantzer, Kurt F.
      Paransky, Ronald
      Parker, Glidden
      Parker, Harry
      Peabody, Laurence
      Pearson, Norman Holmes
      Pepsico Incorporated
      Perutz, George
      Peters, DeWitt
      Peyre, Henri
      Pickett, Clarence E.
      Pierson, -----
      Pike, Merwyn
      Pimpaneau, J.
      Place, Mary Dee
      Pollitzer, Eric
      Pool, Mary Jane
      Popowski, Stella
      Porter, Eliot
      Post, Emily
      Pottasch, Alan M.
      Power, Alan
      Power, E. J.
      Pratt, Vera C.
      Price, Marilyn
      Prince, Alfred M.
      Pritchard, James C.
      Pulitzer, Joseph
    - Parker, Chris, 1971-1974 (Box 23, Folder 62)
    - Picarello, Frank Jr., 1964-1965, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 63)
    - Pinya, Josep, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 64)
    - Prentice, David, 1964-1965 (Box 23, Folder 65)
    - R, 1951-1978; (3 folders) (Box 23, Folder 66-68)
      Rabin, Nathan
      Randolph, Frank
      Randolph, Maxine
      Rankine, Vivi
      Rather, Jane
      Raupple, Nancy
      Ray, Rudolf
      Rayner, Emily
      Referendum 70
      Reinhardt, Anna
      Reisman, Marshall
      Ret, Etienne
      Retray, Catherine
      Reynolds Aluminum
      Ribicoff, Belle Krasne
      Rikko, -----
      Ritchie, Jane
      Robbins, Danny
      Roberts, Elinor
      Roberts, Josie
      Robertson, Brian
      Robinson, John-David
      Rockefeller, David
      Rockefeller, Nelson
      Rockefeller, Sydney
      van Roijen, Robert D.
      Romney, Richard
      Roos, Beatrice Adams
      Root, Diane
      Rose, Barbara
      Rose, Stanley I.
      Rosenberg, Mrs. Albert
      Rothstein, Barbarie
      Roukes, Nicholas
      Rowland, Susan
      Ruttenberg, Mrs. D.
    - Rudkin, Mark, 1960-1977 (Box 23, Folder 69)
    - S, 1947-1978; (4 folders) (Box 23, Folder 70-73)
      Saddler, Juanita Jane
      Salinas, Baruj
      Saunders, Silvia
      Savell, Isabelle K.
      Sawyer, Kenneth
      Scales, Ann Chapman
      Schechter, Pearl
      Schemp, Theodore
      Schlanger, Irving
      Schlapp, George H.
      Schlumberger, Pierre
      Schmerer, David
      Schmolka, Leo L.
      Schneckenburger, Manfred
      Schneider, Albert K.
      Schoonover, Margaret
      Schwartz, Nancy
      Seibu Department Store, Ltd.
      Seid, Dui
      Sekula, Bela
      Sekula, Debbie
      Seligmann, Kurt
      Seuphor, Michel
      Shapiro, Kate
      Sharpe, Mary Elizabeth
      Shaw, Barbara
      Sheen, Rev. Fulton J.
      Shepherd, Judith P.
      Sherman, Frank
      Sherwood, Brenton
      Shriver, Mr. and Mrs. Sargent
      Sikelianos, Eve
      Silver, Caroll M.
      Simmonds, Harvey
      Simpson, Helen
      Smith, Annette Cox
      Smith, Anthony
      Smith/Hooven, Jolly and Nan
      Smyth, Urquhart and Marckwald, Inc.
      Sneed, Andy
      Solomon, Jairaj
      Sparks, Mrs. Harold
      Stanley, Leonard
      Stanley, Sarah V.
      Stars for Freedom
      Stephan, Ruth
      Stephens, Kay
      Stetson, John C.
      Stewart, Constance
      Stillman, Rufus C.
      Stoney, Isabelle
      Story, Ala
      Strasser, Gary
      Sturtevant, Elaine
      Swan, Simone
      Swann, Ingo
      Sykes, Mrs. Gerald
      Sze, Mr. and Mrs. Kenneth C.
    - Shepley, Lili (Mrs. Philip), 1960-1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Solomon Burke, 1964-1971; (2 folders) (Box 24, Folder 2-3)
    - Sturman, George, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - T, 1948-1977 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      Taggert, William
      Talbot, Jonathan
      Tapie, Michel
      Tarig (?)
      Taylor, Brie
      Taylor, Harwood
      Taylor, John Lloyd
      Teetz, Hans J.
      Thomas, Jonathan
      Thompson, Susanne Mason
      Tiffany and Co.
      Tiemer, Gertrude
      Tracy, Lois
      Tremaine, Mrs. Burton
      Trovato, Joseph S.
      Truman, Jock
      Tsingos, Thanos
      Tuck, Albert E.
      Tumarkin, Igal
    - Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - U-V, 1967, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      Ulrich, Alberto
      Villa, Roy
    - W, 1945-1975 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      Wagstaff, Sam
      Walford, Lucille
      Walton, Richard Guy
      Warner, Sylvia Townsend
      Washburn, Gordon
      Washburn, Ruth
      Weidenfeld, Lady
      Weissman-Kuhl, Bari
      Weyschmid, Rita
      Whitford-Carter, Marjorie
      Wight, Mr.
      Williams, Hopie
      Wilson, Emily
      Winston, Mrs. Harry Lewis
      Wolff, Geoffrey
    - Y-Z, 1965-1976 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      Yaddo
      Yajima, Yui (?)
      Yates, Virginia
      Young, Arthur M.
      Young and Rubicam, Inc.
      Zuckerman, Paul
      Zadkine, Ossip
  - Publishers, Newspapers and Magazines, 1946-1978; 3.3
    Files consist of correspondence with various publishers, newspapers, and magazines, concerning publications and articles on art and artists, Betty Parsons and the gallery, the gallery's stable of artists, and her responses. Also covered are advertising, reproductions of art work and purchase of prints for illustrations, and various printing and publishing projects.
    Files are arranged alphabetically by name of publisher or publication. In instances where the name of a publisher contains the name of an individual, the file is arranged alphabetically according to the surname of the individual (for instance, correspondence with Harry N. Abrams, Inc. is filed under "A"). Though unusual, this means of alphabetizing may have originated with the creator and therefore no attempt has been made to modify it.
    - A, 1966-1975 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      Harry N. Abrams, Inc.
      The Art Gallery Magazine
      Art News
      Art Now
      Art Press
      Artforum
      Artists' Postcards
      Arts Magazine
      Art/World
    - Art International, 1962-1973 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - C, 1966-1978 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      Canadian Art
      Christian Science Monitor
      City Woman
      Collectors Press
      Conde Nast
      Connex Systems, Inc.
    - E-F, 1946-1974 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      Editions Alecto Limited
      Editions Encyclopediques Alpha
      Edizioni Hyperion
      Encyclopedia Britannica
      Field Enterprises Educational Corporation
      Fortune
    - Fratelli Fabri Editori, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - G-H, 1962-1977 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      Groupement d'Interet Economique du Livre et du Disque
      H. K. Press
      The Hamlyn Group
      Hart's Guide to New York
      Hodder and Stoughton Limited
      Holt, Rinehart and Winston, Inc.
      House and Garden
    - K-M, 1950-1972 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      Das Kunstwerk
      The Letter Edged in Black Press
      Life
      Mademoiselle
      The Massachusetts Review
      McGraw Hill
      Modern Art Annual
      The Museum of Modern Art
    - N-P, 1951-1978 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      Newsweek
      The New York Times
      Northern Virginia Community College
      Noyes Press
      Pictures on Exhibit
      Pictures Publishing Co. (Charles Z. Offin)
      Playboy
      Praeger Publishers, Inc. (formerly Frederick A. Praeger, Inc.)
      Prentice-Hall, Inc.
    - R-T, 1951-1978 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      Nelson Rockefeller Publications, Inc.
      The Earl Rowland Foundation
      Scala Fine Arts Publishers, Inc.
      Seventeen Magazine
      Frederick Teuscher, Inc.
      Thames and Hudson Ltd.
      Time, Inc.
      Town and Country
    - W, 1963-1973 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      Washington International Art Letter
      The Washington Post
      Watson-Guptill Publications
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979-1983; 3.4
    This is the correspondence, most from the 1980s, of gallery assistants Deborah Hildreth and Wendy Peterson. Organized chronologically, this correspondence concerns such matters as tax audits and other gallery business, artists seeking representation, and requests for information. Also found is miscellaneous correspondence (scattered greeting cards mostly) addressed to Jack Tilton.
    - Miscellaneous Gallery Correspondence - Deborah Hildreth, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Gallery Correspondence - Wendy Peterson, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Gallery Correspondence - Wendy Peterson, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Gallery Correspondence - Wendy Peterson, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence - Jack Tilton, undated (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Gallery Logs and Telephone and Address Books, 1978-1981; 3.5
    Found here are gallery logs from 1977-1981 and two telephone and address books that are undated. Staff of the Betty Parsons Gallery maintained the gallery logs, which were used primarily to record telephone messages, although the logs also include lists of calls to make, things to do, mail sent, works sold, etc.
    Files are arranged chronologically by year.
    - Gallery Log, 1977-1978; (See box 52) (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Gallery Log [ National Diary for 1978] (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Gallery Log [ 1979 Standard Diary] (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Gallery Log [ 1980 Standard Diary] (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Gallery Log, 1981; (See box 52) (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Telephone and Address Book, circa 1950-1970 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Telephone and Address Book, circa 1980 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Oversize, Gallery Log, 1977-1978; (Scanned with Box 24, F25) (Box 52 (sol))
    - Oversize, Gallery Log, 1981; (Scanned with Box 24, F29) (Box 52 (sol))
- Appraisal Files, 1954-1983; Series 4; (Box 24; 0.4 linear feet)
  Correspondence and forms concern valuations and appraisals, with requests from gallery clients and the Art Dealers Association of America. One folder solely contains appraisal requests and other information from the Art Dealers Association of America from 1982-1983.
  - Appraisals, 1954-1962 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Appraisals, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Appraisals, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Appraisals, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Appraisals, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Appraisals, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Appraisals, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Appraisals, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Appraisals, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Appraisals, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Appraisals, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Appraisals, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Appraisals, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Appraisals, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Appraisals, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Appraisals, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - Appraisals, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Appraisals, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Art Dealers Association of America (Appraisals and Correspondence), 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Conservation Invoices, 1981-1983 (Box 24, Folder 51)
- Sales and Inventory Records, 1946-1981; Series 5; (Boxes 25-28, 51; 2.9 linear feet)
  Found in this series are the records containing detailed information about gallery stock - sales, purchases, inventory, prices, artists' commissions, individual artist accounts, loan and consignment activities, and commission sales shared with other dealers. Multiple formats include invoices, forms, daybooks, ledger books, ledger sheets and inventories. Additional records documenting routine business transactions are located in the general business and financial records and "Artist Sales and Expenses" invoices can be found within the artist files. Documents in this series are a rich resource of information on individual works of art, including provenance and exhibition history. Condition reports are scattered amongst the files.
  Sales and Inventory Records are arranged into four subseries:
  5.1: Sales and Purchase Records
  5.2: Artist Accounts
  5.3: Consignment and Loan Records
  5.4: Gallery Inventories
  - Sales and Purchases, 1946-1981; 5.1
    This suberies provides detailed information about the gallery's sales and, to a lesser extent, purchases of works of art through invoices, ledgers, record books, and summaries. Due to the variety of formats there is a significant duplication of information. There are only three folders of invoices for purchases dating from 1950-1974. Additional information regarding sales can be found in the general ledgers that are located in disbursements and receipts. Of particular interest are summaries of sales of art works by Ad Reinhardt, Jackson Pollock, and Mark Rothko (circa 1952) and summaries of sales to museums from 1946 - 1952.
    The majority of the files are sales invoices. Most invoices include detailed information about the work of art, the name and address of the buyer, price, and date of sales. Sales invoice files are arranged by four access points: artist, buyer, year, and invoice number. Sales invoices arranged by buyer make up the bulk of the invoices and may represent the most complete record of gallery sales. Filing idiosyncrasies exist within this category, primarily when the buyer is an institution or organization. In some instances the invoices and sales related correspondence were filed under the institution/organization name, while in others it was filed by the last name of the primary correspondent.
    Purchase invoices identify the institution or individual from whom a work was purchased and establishes provenance for works that were not acquired directly from the artist. Purchase invoices can also be found scattered amongst the sales invoice files.
    Files are arranged by format.
    - Sales Invoices by Artist (Box 25)
      - Sales Invoices, A-B, 1977-1980 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Sales Invoices, Brennan, Fanny, 1977-1980 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Sales Invoices, C-F, 1973-1980 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Sales Invoices, Francisco, Richard, 1972-1980 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Sales Invoices, G, 1977-1981 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Sales Invoices, Gray, Cleve, 1969-1980 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Sales Invoices, H, 1972-1981 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Sales Invoices, Hall, Lee, 1977-1981 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Sales Invoices, Kawabata, Minoru, 1978-1981 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Sales Invoices, M, 1977-1981 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Sales Invoices, Malpass, Michael, 1977-1980 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Sales Invoices, Moore, Eliza, 1977-1980 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Sales Invoices, Murch, Walter, 1977-1981 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Sales Invoices, Okada, Kenzo, 1968-1981 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Sales Invoices, P-R, 1966-1980 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Sales Invoices, S, 1973-1982 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Sales Invoices, Steinberg, Carl, 1976-1981 (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Sales Invoices, T, 1977-1981 (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Sales Invoices, Taggart, Bill, 1977-1980 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Sales Invoices, Tuttle, Richard, 1972-1981 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Sales Invoices, V-Z, 1977-1981 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Sales Invoices by Buyer (Box 25)
      - Sales Invoices, Abe-All, 1948-1973 (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Sales Invoices, Alt-Are, 1950-1973 (Box 25, Folder 23)
      - Sales Invoices, Arn-Art, 1958-1973 (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Sales Invoices, Ash-Axi, 1949-1975 (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Sales Invoices, Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1956-1972 (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Sales Invoices, Bab-Bak, 1954-1980 (Box 25, Folder 27)
      - Sales Invoices, Bal-Ban, 1954-1974 (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Sales Invoices, Barc-Bart, 1950-1973 (Box 25, Folder 29)
      - Sales Invoices, Bas-Bei, 1949-1973 (Box 25, Folder 30)
      - Sales Invoices, Ben-Berm, 1953-1975 (Box 25, Folder 31)
      - Sales Invoices, Bern-Bin, 1947-1975 (Box 25, Folder 32)
      - Sales Invoices, Bir-Blo, 1950-1974 (Box 25, Folder 33)
      - Sales Invoices, Blu-Box, 1946-1975 (Box 25, Folder 34)
      - Sales Invoices, Bra-Bro, 1951-1970 (Box 25, Folder 35)
      - Sales Invoices, Buc-Byr, 1950-1980 (Box 25, Folder 36)
      - Sales Invoices, Cab-Car, 1947-1970 (Box 25, Folder 37)
      - Sales Invoices, Cas-Chu, 1948-1974 (Box 25, Folder 38)
      - Sales Invoices, Cin-Coh, 1952-1975 (Box 25, Folder 39)
      - Sales Invoices, Col-Coo, 1954-1977 (Box 25, Folder 40)
      - Sales Invoices, Cop-Cow, 1950-1973 (Box 25, Folder 41)
      - Sales Invoices, Cra-Cus, 1952-1974 (Box 25, Folder 42)
      - Sales Invoices, Carnegie Institute, 1958-1971 (Box 25, Folder 43)
      - Sales Invoices, Chase Manhattan Bank, 1959-1974 (Box 25, Folder 44)
      - Sales Invoices, Dac-Day, 1950-1972 (Box 25, Folder 45)
      - Sales Invoices, Dee-Det, 1949-1975 (Box 25, Folder 46)
      - Sales Invoices, Dew-Din, 1951-1974 (Box 25, Folder 47)
      - Sales Invoices, Dir-Dwy, 1948-1976 (Box 25, Folder 48)
      - Sales Invoices, Daniels, Alfred H., 1963-1975 (Box 25, Folder 49)
      - Sales Invoices, Eag-Eld, 1951-1979 (Box 25, Folder 50)
      - Sales Invoices, Elk-Eps, 1952-1974 (Box 25, Folder 51)
      - Sales Invoices, Equ-Eyr, 1956-1974 (Box 25, Folder 52)
      - Sales Invoices, Fai-Fei, 1952-1973 (Box 25, Folder 53)
      - Sales Invoices, Fen-Fis, 1948-1971 (Box 25, Folder 54)
      - Sales Invoices, Fla-Fle, 1958-1974 (Box 25, Folder 55)
      - Sales Invoices, Fli-Fran, 1947-1979 (Box 25, Folder 56)
      - Sales Invoices, Fras-Ful, 1954-1971 (Box 25, Folder 57)
      - Sales Invoices, G-Gay, 1952-1975 (Box 25, Folder 58)
      - Sales Invoices, Gek-Giz, 1952-1975 (Box 25, Folder 59)
      - Sales Invoices, Gla-Gou, 1952-1975 (Box 25, Folder 60)
      - Sales Invoices, Gra-Gro, 1953-1974 (Box 25, Folder 61)
      - Sales Invoices, Gru-Gut, 1947-1975 (Box 25, Folder 62)
      - Sales Invoices, Hag-Ham, 1952-1973 (Box 25, Folder 63)
      - Sales Invoices, Han-Haz, 1949-1973 (Box 25, Folder 64)
      - Sales Invoices, Heb-Hig, 1950-1974 (Box 25, Folder 65)
      - Sales Invoices, Hil-Hop, 1950-1975 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Sales Invoices, Hor-Hym, 1949-1975 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Sales Invoices, Hilles, Frederick W., 1954-1973 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Sales Invoices, I, 1950-1975 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Sales Invoices, Jab-Jel, 1949-1973 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Sales Invoices, Jen-Joy, 1951-1975 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Sales Invoices, Kah-Kat, 1958-1974 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Sales Invoices, Kau-Kel, 1949-1972 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Sales Invoices, Ken-Klu, 1949-1977 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Sales Invoices, Kui-Kur, 1947-1981 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Sales Invoices, Lad-Lan, 1955-1974 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Sales Invoices, Lar-Lei, 1946-1975 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Sales Invoices, Lem-Lip, 1947-1980 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Sales Invoices, Lis-Lon, 1949-1973 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Sales Invoices, Loo-Lut, 1950-1975 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Sales Invoices, Maa-Mak, 1947-1975 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Sales Invoices, Mal-Marc, 1951-1971 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Sales Invoices, Mare-May, 1952-1973 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Sales Invoices, Maz-McN, 1951-1975 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      - Sales Invoices, Mea-Met, 1951-1977 (Box 26, Folder 20)
      - Sales Invoices, Mey-Mil, 1948-1975 (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Sales Invoices, Min-Mon, 1948-1978 (Box 26, Folder 22)